MEHMET BATUHAN YILMAZ

I am a 2019 English Architecture graduate.

I can develop projects with React.js - Vue.js libraries.

Besides HTML5/CSS3, I am proficient in Tailwind and Bootstrap libraries.

I received Manual Testing Expertise and UX/UI Training.

I have knowledge of management and control systems such as Jira, Confluence, Postman, Swagger and Figma, Adobe Graphic Design programs.

- Front-end Developer
- Manual / Automation Testing Expertise
- <u>UI/UX Design</u>

I am actively looking for a job position.



- mbatuhanylmz@gmail.com
- 05340710261
- 03/11/1996
- İstanbul/Kartal

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Bab Iot Technologies - Front-end Developer May 2022 - August 2022

An interface was designed for the user side of our device, which we developed in the IOT technological revolution, and I took part in UI / UX and Frontend coding in this process. I worked in the company on a project basis. (Figma-Zeplin-Photohop-Vue.js-React.js)

• <u>Getasis IT Technologies - Front-end Developer</u> March 2022 - May 2022

It is the project that I took part in engineering interface development studies at Schneider Electric company as an outsource.

<u>Papirus Digital - Jr. Frontend Developer</u> August 2021 - December 2021

In the company where I worked as a volunteer intern, I provided visual-design and front-end support.

Kodluyoruz & Patika.dev Front-end Developer Education Program September 2021 - November 2021

I took a training program and graduated from Zemin Istanbul with team project work and got a certificate.

EDUCATION

Architecture - English,

İstanbul Okan University

'14-'19

Management Information Systems - DEF,

Anadolu University

'20- '24

Kodluyoruz & Patika.dev

Front-end Developer Education Program

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript
- React.js Vue.js Tailwind Bootstrap
- Git GitHub Jira Confluence
- Swagger Postman
- Adobe Photoshop / Illustrator / XD Figma

LANGUAGES

- English (Upper Intermediate B2+)
- German/ Deutsch (Elementary / Anfanger A2)

REFERENCES

Özkan Küçük CEO & CoFounder - Papirus Digital +90 532 734 48 38

Ali Akdurak CTO - Bab Iot Technologies +90 554 821 77 83